怪兽卡车
特拉维克斯能源公司
窦德 你知道我讨厌什么吗？
Dowd. Now, what do I hate?
无聊的地方
Boring places.
还有呢？
And?
油井打不出油
Wells that aren't pumping oil.
到底怎么回事？
So what's happening?
其他人想太多了
Probably our people being overly cautious.
这根本没什么
I'm sure it's nothing.
最好是这样
It better be.
全公司都把钱押在这里了
I bet the whole company on this site.
这块油田在地底数百尺
Well, the reserve is several hundred feet deeper,
必须穿越
but we have to pass through
一大片水域才能取得油藏
what appears to be a large pocket of water to reach it.
水域？继续钻就是了
Water? Well, let's keep going.
这就是你叫我来的原因？
Is that why you called me down here?
在地底两哩发现水
Discovering water two miles below the surface
深具科学意义
is important, scientifically.
你是首席科学家
Dowd, you're lead scientist here.
- 你怎么看？- 这没什么
- Do we care about that? - No.
有水域
If there's a water pocket,
就可能有生态系统和生命
there's a possibility of an ecosystem. Life.
不可能
Okay. Actually, it's basically impossible.
那里的水压极高
The water pressure at that depth is 10,000 psi.
这些富含氮的水
That water is supersaturated with nitrogen.
缺乏生命所需的营养
There would be no nutrients for life.
还会继续钻吧？
So we keep going, yes?
对 继续钻
Yeah. Punch through.
生物冷光
Bio luminescence.
有生命存在
There is life.
不 那只是…
No, that's...
灯光的反射
That's the reflection from our light.
什么东西？
What was that?
警告
Warning.
钻井导致油井失衡
The bore into the pocket destabilized the well.
压力一下子升高
The pressure's rising way too fast.
底下有生物
There's something down there.
快停止
We have to shut it down. Shut it down!
有东西从油井冲出来
Something came up. Something came up through the well!
这是什么东西？
What is this thing?
他还真是积极
He's a real go-getter.
很多人推荐他
He comes highly recommended.
柏克先生
Mr. Burke!
控制下来了吗？
Do you have this under control?
我们抓到一只
We got this one.
还在找其他两只
I have a search party looking for the other two.
搜查工作要秘密进行
It is very important that you keep your search discreet.
鱼类和野生动物局光发现角蜥
The Department of Fish and Wildlife will shut us down
就会叫我们停工 更何况是这个
over a horned lizard, let alone these things.
慢着 找人来研究这些生物
Wait. Wait. Wait. We gotta get somebody to examine it.
搞懂它的饮食和习性
We find out what it eats, and needs to survive.
再来诱杀其他只
It'll help us find the missing ones and eliminate them.
就算数量不只这些
Also, if there's more where they came from,
我们也搞得定
we'll know what we're dealing with.
聪明 但是要秘密进行
That is smart. But just you.
好 包在我身上
Okay. I'm on it.
地底下都是石油
We are standing on an ocean of oil.
把这件事压下去 我们会大赚一笔
If we keep this quiet, we will all make out very well.
好的
Okay.
交给我来办
I'm on it.
别让它脱离你的视线
Don't let it out of your sight.
耶
Yeah!
石油公司让一些人变有钱
So Terravex made some people rich around here.
很重要呢
Big deal. It doesn't matter.
将就点
We're making do.
别因为他们没来租地就不爽
You shouldn't cry just 'cause you didn't get a land lease from an oil company.
不爽？
Who's crying?
我才不稀罕
Wouldn't take money from Terravex, anyways.
他们毁了这地方
They ruined this town.
你说得好像过去很繁荣
You're talking like you're old enough to remember how it used to be.
这里从来没有好过啊
It was never anything to shout about.
至少爸爸不会离开
Dad was still here.
我会去便利商店
I'm gonna stop at the Loaf 'N Go on the way home.
有什么想买的？
You want anything?
一辆车 让我逃离这个鬼地方
Something with four wheels that'll get me out of this place.
噢
Oh.
长得那么帅
You're so handsome.
怎么没有女生来追你呢？
Where are all the girls knocking down your door?
我今天晚班 明天见啰
I'm closing again tonight, so I won't see you till tomorrow.
你吃一片冷冻披萨 留一片给瑞克
Just one frozen pizza. You save the other one for Rick.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 怎么样？- 很好 对不起
- How you doing? - Good. Sorry.
- 不用 - 好吧 再见
- No. - Okay. Bye.
好的
All right.
崔普
Tripp.
她说很晚才会回来
She said she's not going to be home till late.
有问题吗？
Yeah? Why would that matter?
我回来还会看到你吗？
You're still going to be here when I get back?
别担心 我一直都会在
Don't you worry! I'm not going anywhere.
你也太入神了吧
You enjoy that a little too much.
哪里来的？
Where'd this come from?
潘克斯卡岩
Pankeska Rock.
钻井发生大意外
Big accident up there at the drill site.
天很快黑
It got late pretty quick.
明天再弄
Let's strip it tomorrow.
我有回来的话
If I come back.
别以为是你在帮我
Don't think you're doing me a favor being here.
我不需要施舍
I don't take charity.
我也不需要
Neither do I.
这是6.4公升HemiV8引擎
This is a 6.4 liter Hemi V-8.
也只有这个可以用吧
Probably the only piece worth anything.
拿去吧
Go ahead, it's yours.
大概也只有你可以修得好
Ha. If anyone can get it working, you can.
帮我锁好这里
Hey, lock up for me.
老浩克已经不管用了
Old Hulk ain't what he used to be.
我帮你弄个425匹马力
I got 425 horsepower for you, buddy.
虽然不是全镇最酷的
You're not gonna be the prettiest thing in town,
但是你有一颗强大的心脏
but you're going to have the heart of an elephant in you.
冲过那座火山？一定可以的 总统
Outrun that volcano? You bet we can, Mr. President.
哦
Oh.
你在我的卡车做什么？
What are you doing in my truck?
好 我就带你和你妹去音乐季
Yeah, I can take you and your sister to Coachella.
不只一个妹妹？
Oh. Sisters?
干掉他们
Ah! Kill 'em!
启动弹射座椅
Ejector seat engaged.
北达科他KYPN电视台
You're watching KYPN, North Dakota,
您的新闻首选
your number one source for news.
潘克斯卡岩当地居民
Local residents were awakened
被可怕的意外惊醒
by a catastrophic accident at Pankeska Rock,
特拉维克斯石油公司工人忙着灭火
where Terravex Oil workers fought a towering fire
浓密的黑烟笼罩清晨的天空
whose black smoke still filled the morning air.
钻井工人伟德柯利当时就在现场
Rigger Wade Coley was on the scene when the accident happened.
啊…
Ah...
我听到爆炸声
Well, I, uh, heard an explosion
接着井架就垮了
and, uh, the tower crashed, and...
爸？
Dad?
大家尖叫四处逃
...guys were running and shouting,
我只能透露这些
and that's really all I'm allowed to say.
为什么特拉维克斯石油要下禁声令？
Why this shroud of secrecy and silence by Terravex Oil?
我只是听命办事
I just do my job.
我真不知道
I really don't know.
恕无法回答其他问题
I can't answer any more questions.
你在镇上？
You're here?
我向他解释过
I explained to him that the number of objects
周期表的一些元素…
naturally occurring in the periodic table of elements...
崔普 嗨
Tripp! Hey!
呃… 嗨
Oh, uh... Hey.
我是你的生物小老师吧？
We were matched up for biology tutoring?
辅导课都没看到你？
And you haven't showed up to any of the sessions?
你没拿到课表？
Or maybe you didn't get the schedule? Um...
班上有贴 我寄到你信箱
It was posted in class, and I emailed you a copy,
塞进你柜子
and slid one into your locker.
我还没看
Yeah. I just haven't checked it yet.
我懂
Oh, yeah. I mean, I get it.
我也会连续好几天没去看信箱
I go, like, days sometimes without checking my email
或置物柜
or going to my locker.
嗬嗬
Ho-ho!
对了 我是梅芮迪丝
I'm Meredith, by the way.
这我知道
Right. Yeah, I knew that.
嗨 崔普
Hey, Tripp!
山姆 全镇最幸运的小开 怎么样？
Hey, Sam. How's the luckiest kid in town?
我爸不让我碰车
You know my Dad doesn't let me drive the merch.
况且他在气头上
Plus, he's flipping out right now.
怎么了？
What happened?
给你看超扯的东西
You want to see something crazy?
我在留你的发型
See, I'm growing out my hair, like you.
大家会以为是亲兄弟
Hope people don't think we're brothers.
以前也有过
We've had trouble before,
但顶多破个玻璃
but usually it's a rock through the window,
或车尾灯
smashed taillight, that kind of thing.
我就说吧
Check it out.
你肯定没见过
Told you you've never seen anything like this.
油箱被搜刮一空
They ripped out the gas tanks.
谁会干这种事？
I mean, who would even do that?
肯定是流氓拿什么强力工具干的
Well, it has to be vandals. Serious power tools.
崔普 知道吗
Tripp, you know what?
我这里刚好有课表
I happen to have the schedule for our tutoring right here,
下次是星期四和星期五
and it says our next sessions are Thursday and Friday.
这个星期五
This Friday.
我星期五要打工
Uh, I have work Friday.
我去你工作的地方
I can come by your work!
待会见 崔普
See you later, Tripp!
很高兴可以一起玩
Good to hang out with you, bro.
它在最里面 快点
It's on the far side. Here. Come on.
- 哪里？- 那里
- Where is it? - It's in there.
你们要加派人手
We're gonna need more guys.
是什么动物？熊吗？
What is it? A bear?
不是 打开就知道了
No. Just open it up and look.
打开
Grab that.
这些捕集器根本不够
You're going to need, like, 12 more of those things.
在里面
It's in there.
什么都没有
I don't see anything.
什么？
What? No, I...
我把他关在里面 他…
No,no,no. I trapped him in here! He had...
他很大 有触手和一双大
He was huge. He had tentacles and giant
眼睛
eyes.
你们先出去 我来处理
You guys go on ahead. I'll handle this.
我知道你在想什么
Rick, I know what you're thinking,
但你要相信我
but you've got to believe me. He...
他吸光了整桶油
He sucked all the oil out of the can!
- 他吸光了 - 够了没？
- He sucked it out. - Are you done? Huh?
我知道了
I knew it.
我听到是你通报的
I knew it as soon as I heard it was you on the call.
就知道不能相信
I knew something wasn't gonna go right.
你以为这样很好玩吗？
You thought this would be funny, huh?
想糊弄我和其他人？想耍我吗？
Pranking me and my guys? Making me look like an idiot?
我真的看到了
I saw it.
你高兴就好
Yeah. Well, I hope it was fun.
再不好好做人就会像你爸一样
You're gonna wind up just like your dad if you don't straighten out.
不准你说我爸
Don't talk about my dad.
这是最后一次
That's it for you. That's it.
我在这里压力好大 哪里都去不了
I feel so squeezed in here, like trapped.
没拿到奖学金就惨了
Like, I might die here if I don't get one of those scholarships,
念不起外地学校
because we can't afford an out-of-state school.
我无法想像永远待在这里
But there's no way I can imagine staying here, either.
你有看新闻吗？
I mean, did you see that thing on the news?
油井爆炸意外？
About the burning well?
大家都不关心
It's like, nobody cares
环境破坏 反正
about how much damage they're doing to the environment because
整个小镇都靠特拉维克斯石油赚钱
all the money in town comes from Terravex Oil.
你对生物学很有一套吧？
Hey, you know a lot about biology, right?
不然怎么会当你的小老师？
That's what I'm tutoring you in.
多久会发现一次新物种？
How often do they discover new species?
认真的？
Seriously?
我看过类似节目
I was just watching a show on this.
你看国家地理频道？
Do you watch Nat Geo?
不看
No.
哦
Oh.
好吧 他们说每年都会发现1万5千个新物种
Well, um, they said that they discover, like, 15,000 new species every year.
北达科他有可能出现
So, would it be possible for there to be,
大型海洋生物吗？
like, a giant sea creature here in North Dakota?
很有可能
Technically, totally.
这里曾经沉在海底
This whole state was under an ocean at one point.
理论上
So theoretically,
湖泊深处可能有这类生物
the deep lakes could have something like that.
我是说大型海洋生物跑到陆地上
I mean on land. A giant sea creature on land.
不可能
Well, no.
海洋生物早已适应水生环境
Because its body evolved in a water environment,
陆地上有重力不利它们行走
so it wouldn't be able to move with the effects of gravity pulling on it.
你想看那个节目吗？
Did you want to watch that show?
我有录
'Cause I have it on my DVR.
四点了 待会见
It's 4:00. I'll see you later.
来吧
Come on.
快点啊
嗯？
Hmm?
不会吧
No, no, no.
搞什么
Come on.
快点停止
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
糟了
Shit.
啊
Ugh!
我在帮你啊
I'm trying to help you!
放开我 我救了你啊
Let go of me! I just saved your life!
看到没？你差点被压扁
See? You would have been flat as a pancake,
压得像一片薄饼
you squishy piece of squish!
你到底是什么？
What are you?
你想要油？
You want the oil?
你要答应不会吃掉我
You promise not to eat me?
不要碰我
Hey! Don't even touch me!
太扯了吧
You got to be kidding me.
不要喝太快
You better slow down there.
看你醉醺醺的
You're getting all jacked up.
干嘛？不喜欢那辆车？
What? You don't like that truck?
好 你看着
Okay. Watch this.
看到没？它伤不了你
See? It can't hurt you.
哦
Ooh.
哇哦
Whoa!
有什么需要帮忙的吗？
Can I help you, sir?
我们为特拉维克斯工作
Yeah. We're working for Terravex.
昨晚有东西撞破我们的栅栏
We had something crash through our fences last night.
没人看清楚 只知道体型很大
No one got a good look at it, but it was big, whatever it was.
你们有接获类似的通报吗？
You get any reports of anything like that in the last day?
没有 我们没听说
No, dude, we haven't heard any of that.
没任何异状？
Nothing strange?
没有人通报大型动物？
No calls about seeing some kind of big animal?
废车场好像有怪兽
There was the monster in the junkyard.
或"巨大生物"
Or was it a "giant creature"?
嘿 嘿 伙计们
Hey! Hey! Guys!
不是说了吗？那件事到此为止
What did I say? Enough about that.
我对这个消息很有兴趣
Well, I'd like to hear the story.
没什么好多说的
Well, there's not much to tell.
没什么 只是谎报
It was a false call. That's what it was.
在哪里？
Where from?
112号公路旁的威德斯废车场
It's Weathers' junkyard, off 112.
不是说好了吗？
Hey! We just talked about this.
干嘛这么在意一通谎报电话？
Look, I don't see why you're so worked up about a prank call.
你不也是吗？
I don't see why you are, either.
不要再耍宝了
Oh, quit being a baby.
好了
There we go.
我要把你送去警察局
Let's get you to the sheriff's station.
看瑞克怎么说
See what Rick has to say now.
搞什…？
What the...
嘿 回来
Hey! Get back here!
别动
Hey! Whoa! Stop!
不要动
Stay! Stay put!
别动
Stay put!
听我说…
Listen...
大家都把我的话当耳边风
Nobody's listening to me!
你也没多壮嘛 陆地鱿鱼？
Not so tough, are you now, landsquid?
你真的
You are so
好臭
smelly.
不可以
No. No, no, no.
嘿
Hey!
给我回来
Get back here!
不可以
Oh, no, no, no.
你敢刮伤我的车就糟了
If you scratch my truck, so help me!
有什么事吗？
Can I help you?
我听说昨晚这里有骚动
I understand you had an incident last night,
但警察局不相信你
but the local authorities didn't believe you.
那你为什么感兴趣？
Explain why you care?
我们在找一个奇怪又
We're looking for something unusual.
危险的东西
Something dangerous.
要拿它干嘛？
What are you looking to do with it?
确保它不会伤害到人
Make sure it doesn't hurt no one.
我只有听到声音 没有亲眼看到
Well, I thought I heard something. I didn't see anything.
八成是土狼之类的吧
Must have been a coyote, or something like that.
那只土狼还有再来吗？
Did this coyote come back?
没有
No.
我们可以进去看看吗？
Mind if we take a look?
可以
Yes, actually.
你们不应该闯入私人用地 但是
Because it's private property and you're not allowed to go in there,
想看就看吧
but, uh, go ahead and look around, if you want to.
我就通融你们一次
I can make an exception this time.
哦
Oh.
我看到的 我听到的土狼…
You know, uh, the coyote that I saw... I heard, was, um...
应该是从废车场另一侧来的
I think it came from that side of the yard.
我很确定
Uh... For sure, actually.
废车场另一侧？
From that side of the yard?
呃… 对
Uh... Yeah.
别闹了
Stop it! Stop it!
可以不要动吗？
Will you stop?
把这里搜刮一遍
Search the whole place.
电瓶没电
Ah. The battery's dead.
我要推去其他车库
I'm going to push it over to the other garage.
请自便
You guys just keep looking around.
嘿
Hey!
把卡车还给我
Give me back my truck!
嘿
Hey!
把卡车还给我
Give me back my truck!
崔普？
Tripp?
我做了教学卡片
I made flash cards!
梅芮迪丝？
Meredith?
你在干…
What are you...
说真的 现在不是时候
Look, seriously, now is a really bad time.
好吧
Oh, okay.
你可以载我回家吗？
Do you think you could give me a ride home?
我住得不远
I don't live too far away.
但晚上走回去有点可怕
But it was kind of a scary walk in the dark.
我没有车
I, uh... I don't have a car.
它不会跑
It doesn't run.
这不是…
It's not...
你可以快点回家吗？
Uh... Can you, uh, just go home?
拜托你
Please.
你不送我回家很没礼貌啊
It's kind of rude of you not to give me a ride home.
我星期五晚上跑来这里
I came all the way over here on Friday night
教你功课
to help you study,
你却赶我走？
and you're just sending me away?
我被绑架怎么办？
How would you feel if I got abducted on my way home?
谁会绑架你？
Who's gonna abduct you?
我不是那个意思
It's not what I mean.
这里治安那么好
It just... It doesn't happen out here.
那是什么声音？
What was that?
我也听到了
I heard it, too.
小子
Hey, kid!
你要打P档
You should probably put that in park.
嗨 上车吧
Hey! Why don't you just get in the truck?
- 真的吗？- 对 上车
- Really? - Yeah. Just get in.
噢…
Oh...
哇哦
Whoop! Oh!
听我说 奇怪的事正在发生
Listen, there's something going on here.
真的吗？
Really?
很夸张
Yeah, something crazy.
我自己也无法解释
And I don't even know how to begin to explain it.
不需要解释
You don't have to. I mean...
我也有同样的感觉
I feel it, too.
不是那样的
Uh, no...
我是说…
There's...
硬着头皮上了
Just go if you're going to go!
冲啊
Go!
那小子肯定知道什么
That kid knows something.
我会开手排 不然换我开
You know, I can drive manual if you don't know how.
好了 走到底右转
Okay. Well, at the end of the hill, turn right.
右转 我说右转
Right! I said right!
我在试了
I'm trying!
- 停车 - 我停不下来
- Stop the car! - I can't! Nothing's working.
啊
Ah!
- 双手握着方向盘 - 我…
- Put your hands on the wheel! - I...
没有用
This isn't doing anything!
我知道
Yeah. I know!
啊…
Whoa...
前面有树
Tree, tree, tree!
那条柏油路可以通往我家
There's a paved road that goes to my house.
你有驾照吗？
Do you even have your license?
嘘
Shh.
车子该不会是偷来的？
Did you just steal this? Did we just steal this?
好了 下车
Okay, get out!
听到没？
You hear me?
出来
Get out!
是你推我上车的啊
You were the one who pushed me into your truck!
把卡车还给我
Give me my truck back!
你在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
他
That!
哇哦
Whoa!
是蛇吗？
Whoa! Was that a snake?
崔普 那是什么？
Tripp, what is that?
你自己看
Take a look and see.
看什么？
Take a look?
他不会伤害你
He won't hurt you.
什么
What!
我的天啊 那是什么？
Oh, my gosh. What is that?
崔普
Tripp!
算了 你留着吧
Ah! Fine, just keep the truck!
你说你家很近 我们走
You said you live close, right? Let's go.
你是要…
Are you just gonna...
说真的 崔普 那到底…
I mean, seriously, Tripp, what...
它会 让卡车移动
It's, uh, moving the truck.
好吧
Okay.
我爸很少来这里
My dad barely comes in here,
所以你待一个晚上应该没关系
so you should be fine for the night.
我可以借用这里的工具吗？
Think he'd mind if I borrowed some of this stuff?
我会付钱给你爸
I'll pay him back.
他应该不会发现 但你想干嘛？
I doubt he'd even notice. But for what?
我要把这家伙弄出来
So I can pry Creature here out of my truck.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
我的门禁还有两分钟 所以…
Yeah. My curfew is in, like, two minutes, so...
谢谢你让我度过超级诡异的夜晚
Thank you for the incredibly weird night!
不要让它靠近我的马
Please don't let it near my horse.
好
Okay.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey!
不要动可以吗？
Sit still, would you?
嘿
Hey!
噢
Oh.
堵住油藏的不只是这个水域
Now, it's not just this one pocket that's blocking our oil.
还有几百万年
It is a massive, interconnected ecosystem,
不受侵扰的大型生态系统
untouched for millions of years.
那种生物
I mean, it's basically a certainty
肯定不只这几只
that there are more of those things down there.
可以在水陆呼吸的史前两栖类
Prehistoric amphibians, that can breathe water or air,
居住在错综复杂的地底湖泊和洞穴
living in a network of underground lakes and caves.
看来尼斯湖水怪不是天方夜谭
It's like the Loch Ness Monster isn't a myth after all.
还有其他钻井的方法吗？
Can we access it?
地表有火山口湖
Well, there's a crater lake on the surface,
火山口会直接通到地底
and, yeah, the vents that feed the lake lead directly down there.
- 我们的设备过得去吗？- 嗯
- Could we get equipment there? - Hmm.
开我的吉普车过去很颠簸
Well, it was a pretty rough drive in my Jeep.
过了矿场有土路
There's a good dirt road after the strip mine,
之后就没路了
but after that it's all off-road.
很好
Good job.
那几只生物呢？
What about our POWs?
还在找第三只
Well, we're still working on it,
只要它还活着
but if that third one is alive out there somewhere,
一定找得到
We'll find it.
住手 过去一点
Stop! Stop. Give me some space.
- 早安 - 早安
- Morning. - Morning.
你没赶走他
So, instead of getting him out of there,
反而把他关在里面
you built more stuff to keep him in.
这家伙很厉害
This thing is kind of awesome.
又壮又聪明 超聪明的
Like, strong and smart. Really smart.
他学什么东西都很快
He can learn anything, fast.
我给他取了名字 对不对？曲奇
Oh, and I gave him a name. Isn't that right, Creech?
你叫他曲奇？
You named him Creech?
他的触手有一些像毛发的东西
He's got these hair-like things on its tentacles.
纤毛对吧？
Cilia, right?
可以产生巨大的扭力
They can generate a massive amount of torque,
我在轮轴弄些凹槽
especially once I scored the axles
让他比较好抓
to make more surface area to grip.
每个轮胎都这样
And that's at each tire.
想像有很多个
So, imagine the angular velocity
差速器会有多快
when it's not all spread out from one differential.
你不笨嘛
You're not dumb.
什么？
What?
没事
Nothing.
嗯…
Um...
既然这样…
So...
我只要踩油门
I press the gas,
油门线就会拉起控制杆 打开防护罩
the throttle wire pulls these levers, which open these blinders.
对不对？
Right? Right?
就好像
It's like
这辆车是他的轮椅
the truck's a wheelchair for it.
不是啦 就像是…
Uh, no. It's like...
他是这辆卡车的引擎
It is an engine for my truck.
你看我
Watch.
没错就是这样
Yes! Yes! Yes!
看到没？
Did you see that?
好了
Okay.
嘿
Hey!
看起来不难嘛
See, it's not so hard.
好了
Okay.
冲吧
Come on.
你成功了
You got it!
哇
Whoo!
耍帅
Show-off!
太扯了
No way!
哇哦
Whoa!
可以把车子抬起来吗？
Lift this up, would you?
别闹了
Stop.
这不算小事吧？
But this thing is important, right?
难道不应该告诉其他人？
Shouldn't we tell somebody?
然后让人们乱戳
You think he'll be better off with somebody poking at him,
调查他是什么吗？
trying to figure out what he is?
首先 你怎么确定他是男生？
First of all, how do you know that it's a "he"?
再来我身为动物权青年队的成员
And secondly, as a Youth for Animal Rights activist,
有义务为动物的福祉负责
I feel responsible for the well-being of that animal.
他很好 过得很开心
He's fine. He's happy.
嘿
Hey!
别闹了
Hey, stop!
我是说他有故乡
I'm just saying, he came from somewhere.
或有家
He has a home.
你不觉得他会想回家吗？
Don't you think he wants to go back there?
当然 但他在这里很安全
Sure, but he's safe in here in the meantime.
况且他玩得很开心
Besides, he's having fun.
就像拥有第一部三轮车的小朋友
He's like a kid with his first tricycle.
我要去潘克斯卡岩找我爸
I'm going to see my dad at Pankeska.
出事的时候他在潘克斯卡岩？
Was he at Pankeska Rock when that accident happened?
对
Yeah.
我跟你去
I'm coming with you.
好 曲奇 吃饭啰
Okay, Creech, let's get you fed.
我会还你的
I'll get you back.
呃…
Uh...
好极了
Great.
嘿
Hey!
你的卡车蛮酷的
I like your truck.
这什么玩意？
What is this?
你知道看起来像什么吗？
You know what this looks like?
载满垃圾的垃圾车
This looks like if a garbage truck took a dump.
真不是普通的蠢 蠢到没药医了
And not like a normal dump. Like a really bad one.
看起来就是这样
That's what this looks like.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - Anytime.
这么贵
Ouch.
你不觉得声音很奇怪吗？
That sound weird to you?
卡车怪兽应该有
How is a monster living in the hood of your car
怎样的声音？
supposed to sound?
可能没事吧
He's probably fine.
为什么一直震动？
Um... Okay. Why is he moving like this?
不知道 他好嗨
I don't know. He's hyper.
怎么回事？
Why would he be hyper all of a sudden?
食物有问题 汽油是油 可是…
It's what he ate. Gasoline is oil, but with...
有其他化学添加物
Added chemicals!
怎么回…
What the...
你最好自己开车
Okay. I think now is a good time to take charge.
放手 我的视野比你好
Let go! I can see better than you.
呃…
Uh...
你在干嘛？缩回去
Hey, what are you doing? Get back in there!
小心
Tripp! Tripp! Watch out!
你在干嘛？
Oh, no. What are you doing?
不 不 不
No, no, no!
快点缩回去 我在开车
Get back in there! I'm driving!
我叫你放手
I said, let go!
天啊 我碰到他的眼睛
Oh, gosh, I touched his eye!
二手车
别闹了
No, no, no.
看我怎么卖烂车给吊带裤老头
Watch me unload this lemon on Old Man Overalls here.
千万不要
No! No! No!
算了 右转
Okay. Right!
对不起
Sorry.
好 新规定
Okay, new rule,
不喂曲奇吃汽油
no feeding Creature gasoline.
你不喜欢细菌培养基？
So, you don't like the bacteria cultures, huh?
线虫呢？
How about nematodes?
也不喜欢
Don't like those, either.
嗯
Hmm.
好吧
Well...
你在石油层底下总要吃点什么吧
You must eat something out there under those oil beds.
你好
Hi.
爸？
Dad?
爸
Hey, Dad.
我是崔普
It's Tripp.
崔普？
Tripp.
真的是你 看看你
Well, it sure is. Look at you.
我不想弄脏你
Ah. Don't want to get my grime all over you.
好吧
Right.
你的？
This yours?
是啊
Yeah.
我是问车子 我知道她是你女朋友
The truck, not the girl. I figured the girl's yours.
不算是
No. Not really.
嗨 我是梅芮迪丝
Hi. I'm Meredith.
伟德
Wade.
不赖喔
This is something.
看起来很棒
This is solid.
做得不错
This is solid work.
谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
来坐坐
Come on up.
车子停在我的拖车旁边吧
Why don't you park it at my trailer?
我跟同事说我不去酒吧了
I'm just gonna call my guys, tell them I won't be at the bar.
好啊
Yeah.
很小 但至少有屋顶和床
It's small, but it's a roof and a bed.
这只是暂时的吧？
It's only temporary for work, right?
你有固定住所吗？
I mean, you have a permanent place somewhere?
这已经够我用了
Uh, yeah, well, this does the job.
我待在家时间不多
I'm not inside much, anyway.
每次轮班都半天了
They got us working 12-hour shifts.
意外发生时你在现场吗？
Were you working when, uh, that accident happened?
对
Oh, yeah.
网络有很多传言
There's all these rumors I read online about it.
真相到底是什么？
What happened?
你们不要说出去喔
This stays in here, all right?
- 好的 - 好的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
他们那天晚上从地底挖东西
They drug something out of the ground that night.
结果推得太深
Pushed so far down,
地球就不爽了 释放出坏东西
it was like the earth got mad and let something bad out.
但他们说只是天然气
But they say it was a pocket of gas,
我就当它是啰
so I guess it was a pocket of gas, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
不然还能怎样？
What do I know?
对吧？
Right?
我东西在车上忘了拿
I left something on the bus.
等我回来
You guys stay here, I'll be right back.
一起吃鸡翅
We'll have some wings.
至少我们知道曲奇是从哪里来的
Well, at least we know where that thing came from.
那天晚上的人肯定跟特拉维克斯有关
Those guys the other night must have been from Terravex.
他们不想让这个生物曝光
They don't want anyone to know about the creature.
只要油田上面有新物种
Well, they wouldn't be able to drill
他们就不能钻井了
if there was some new species living on top of the oil.
我去看看曲奇
I'm gonna go check on him.
不要放他自己在那
Probably not good to leave him alone long.
爸？
Dad?
这些人想找你聊聊
These men want to have a word with you, Tripp.
他们想要回这辆车
They want their truck back.
要回去？那是我组装的
Their truck? I built that!
你妈昨天打电话给我
Look. Your mother called me last night.
她看到我上电视
She saw me on TV,
心想你会来找我
thought you'd maybe come up here and try to find me.
你出卖我 就为了这些人
You sold me out. To them.
我没有出卖你
I'm not selling you out to no one.
我只是做最好的决定
I just wanna do what's best.
对谁来说最好？
For who?
- 我们只是想跟你聊聊 - 别靠近我
- We just want to talk to you, son. - Watch it!
我不会跟你走
I'm not going anywhere with you!
你会的
Yes, you are.
听他的
Just listen to him, Tripp.
你们又不是警察
You're not the police.
凭什么带走他
You don't have the right to take him.
这是我们的私人用地
This is private property. Our private property.
放开我
Get off of me!
快上车 快上车
Get in the truck. Get in the truck.
你以为我不敢动你
I'll hurt you, kid.
我会的
I will.
那东西在卡车里
It's the truck! That thing is in the truck!
我快到了
Yeah, I'm just pulling in now.
你不要担心好吗？
Listen, I don't want you to worry, okay?
如果他在那里 我会带他回家吃晚餐
If he's here, I'll have him home by dinner.
过去 我来开车
Move over! I'm driving!
是吗？
Oh, really?
我先挂了
I gotta go.
崔普？
Tripp?
哇
Whoo!
好耶
Yes!
崔普
Tripp!
到底在搞什么？
What the heck is going on here?
有大卡车
Big truck,
大卡车 大卡车
big truck, big truck!
崔普
Tripp.
我不要停车 我不会放弃这辆车
No. I'm not stopping and I'm not giving up the truck.
不 开快一点
No. Go faster!
是的 我们找到了
Okay. We got him.
分散包抄他 别让他跑了
Fan out. Cut him off. Don't let him out of town.
- 过不去的 - 可以的
- We're not gonna fit. - I think we can do it.
成功了
It worked!
快后退
Move! Go!
哇
Whoa!
什么？
What?
你教过他吗？
Did you train him to do this?
有
Yes.
啊…
Ah...
我根本不知道他怎么学的？
I have no idea how he learned this.
他爬下来了？
Did that just happen?
对 他办到了
Oh, yeah, it did!
呃…
Uh...
有墙
Wall!
你等着看
Watch this.
噢
Oh!
我们开在屋顶上
Oh... We're driving on a roof.
别挡路 鸽子
Get out of our way, pigeons!
哇 你有看到吗？
Whoa! Did you see that?
抓紧了
Hang on!
不行
No way.
我不想掉下去
I want to stay on the roof now!
听到没？有火车
Did you hear that? The train.
那又怎样？
So what?
它有五哩长
That thing is five miles long.
把他们挡在火车后面
If we can put that in between us and them,
我们可以多争取十分钟
we'll get a 10 minute head start.
要不要考虑B计划？
Oh. How about a plan B?
没时间想B计划了
No time for a plan B.
他们好像跟丢了
Besides, I think we lost them.
"请勿在铁轨逗留"
我们冲不过去的
Tripp, I don't think we're going to make it.
可以的
We'll make it!
再快一点
We're not going fast enough!
减速
Slow down!
刹车
Brakes!
崔普
Tripp!
干得好 曲奇
Yeah! Way to go, Creech!
你干嘛追那个男孩？
Hey! What are you doing, chasing that boy all over my county?
这是私人保全问题
It's a private company security matter!
你危及他人生命
You're putting lives in danger.
你妨碍公务
You're interfering with law enforcement!
我们公司养活镇上每一个人
The company I'm working for employs everyone in this town,
包括你
and that includes you!
下一次选举什么时候 警长？
When's the next election, Sheriff?
滚回去开罚单和赶牛吧
Go back to writing tickets and shooing cows off the road.
你刚刚救了我
You really saved me back there.
谢谢你这个又丑又可爱的大块头
Thanks, you big, ugly, beautiful blob.
我爸只有打猎季节会来 所以…
My dad only uses this during hunting season, so...
- 你说这里有汽油？- 对
- You said there was oil? - Yeah.
用来发电 所以我们会没电
But it's for the generator, so we won't have electricity.
没关系 他应得的
That's okay. He deserves it.
外面比较舒服
It's nicer out here.
我不介意睡外面
Yeah, I don't mind.
你会怕火？
Are you scared of fire?
我喝汽油的话也会怕火
I would be, 1100, if I drank oil.
崔普 你爸的事情我很遗憾
Tripp, I'm sorry about your dad.
反正那个地方也糟透了
It would have been a lousy place to stay, anyways.
我是说
I mean,
他突然变成
how weird would it have been
好人也很怪吧？
if he'd turned out to be a decent guy, right?
怎么可能？
What would that have been like?
但这样就不会有现在的你
You wouldn't be who you are.
而且在我们学校和小镇
And there's no one like you at our school
你是独一无二的人物
or in our town.
所以
So,
这一点要感谢你爸
that's something to thank your dad for, at least.
吓死我了
God!
你要去哪里？
Whoa, whoa, whoa, where are you going?
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
搞什么
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
你在干嘛？
Hey. What are you doing?
嘿
Hey.
不要
No.
我会送你回家
I'm going to get you home.
我保证做到
I promise you that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
好了吗？注意看
Ready? Watch.
你也可以教老鼠做这些事
You could teach a mouse how to do that.
这还不够厉害 厉害的在后头
That's not the amazing part. This is the amazing part.
我没有用石油诱导这一只
I didn't teach that one to do that for the oil.
只有那一只
I taught that one how to do that for the oil.
它们跟蚂蚁或蜜蜂一样拥有群体智慧
They have hive intelligence, like, urn, ants or bees.
只要靠近彼此
When they're in close proximity,
就立刻知道
one of them knows what the other knows,
对方的想法
almost immediately.
它们像燃油引擎一样代谢石油
And they metabolize oil like a combustion engine.
窦德 你在干嘛？
Dowd, what are you doing?
我是科学家
I'm a scientist.
- 我在做科学研究 - 不
- I'm being a scientist. - No.
你爱上它们了
You are falling in love.
就像斯德哥尔摩症候群
This is some sort of Stockholm syndrome.
你搞反了吧
That's backwards.
- 随便啦 - 好吧
- Whatever. - Okay.
我限定两天后 把这两只黏东西跟污水
Look, in two days, our waste water goes to Ohio.
一起送去俄亥俄
The mucous twins go with.
喷射到地底深处的注入井
Going to shoot it down deep into an injection well.
不要留下痕迹
No trace.
它们才不是没脑的蛞蝓
No. They're not like mindless ground slugs.
它们有智慧和情感
They have intelligence, they show emotion.
这样杀了它们不道德吧
It would be unethical to kill them.
不道德
Unethical?
窦德 我们都合作那么久了
Dowd, you and I have been together a long time.
我看你经常扭曲事实
I have seen you stretch the truth,
捏造环保报告
falsify environmental protection reports,
跟媒体说谎
and lie to the media.
我们在同一条船上
We are in this together.
振作一点
Cheer up.
不要随便张扬
And keep those things quiet!
崔普 崔普
Tripp. Tripp!
干嘛？
What are you doing?
他不见了
He's gone.
曲奇
Creech!
他怎么会离开？
Why would he leave?
不知道 但我们要比他们更早找到他
I don't know, but we better find him before they do.
我的手机被带走了
Yeah, well, he took off with my cell phone,
无法找人来接我们
so I can't even call anybody to come pick us up.
没关系 我有
It's okay. I have mine.
慢着 你的手机在车上吗？
Wait, your cell phone's in the truck?
是啊
Yeah.
我用APP追踪他
I have an app. We can track him.
有了
There he is.
他要去哪里？
Where is he going?
我不知道
I don't know.
这里 停在这里
It's here. Stop, stop here.
等一下 特拉维克斯？
Wait. Terravex?
停在这里就好吗？
Are you sure this is far enough?
可以开到最后面吗？
Would you mind dropping us off at the end of the block?
他不在
He's not there.
他可能跑进去了
Maybe he went inside.
那是什么？
What is that?
我不知道
I don't know.
他来救他们
He came here for them.
这就是他离开的原因
That's why he left.
不可以
No, don't! Don't!
去检查三号仓库
Hey, guys, check on warehouse three.
快点住手
No! Stop! Stop!
快拿麻醉枪射它
Slow it down. Tranquilize it!
不
No!
- 不要 - 射它
- Hey! Stop. - Shoot it!
住手
Stop!
你会害死他
Stop! You're killing him!
把它弄起来
Scrape it up.
把这两位带过来
Bring them with me.
你很爱你的猫
Well, you certainly love your cats.
都是猫的照片
It's all cats.
有了
Oh! Here we go.
删除 删除 删除
Delete. Delete. Delete.
删除
Delete.
谢谢
Thank you.
删除照片并无法掩盖事实
You can't just delete pictures and think this goes away.
不然你们要怎样？
Why? What are you going to do?
跟警察说
Go to the police and tell them
有怪兽从油田冲出来？
that there are monsters coming up out of the oil fields?
上次不是被打脸了吗？
How'd that work out for you last time?
听我说
Look.
伤人 不是我的嗜好
Hurting people, is not my thing.
但他很喜欢
It's his.
柏克先生
Mr. Burke,
带他们出去
show these two the highway.
走啊
Let's go!
左转
To your left.
接下来我来就好 谢谢查理
Okay! I'll take them from here. Thanks, Charlie.
坦纳森的命令 都检查好了
Tenneson's orders. So, it all checks out.
走吧
Just keep walking normally.
放开你的手 恶心鬼
Get your hands off us, slimebag.
我一紧张就会流汗
Okay, it's not slime, it's sweat. I sweat when I'm nervous.
谢谢你注意到了
Thanks for calling attention to it. Look.
- 我跟你们是一边的 - 什么？
- I'm on your side. - What?
精神与你们同在
Spiritually.
好啦 我说清楚一点
Okay, I'm messing this up.
我是地质学家
Sorry. I'm a scientist, a geologist.
我想帮你们
But I want to help you.
为什么？
Why'?
我受不了眼睁睁看着他们死掉
Because I can't just stand here and watch them die.
我们干嘛相信你？
And why should we trust you?
这些生物太特别了
Because these creatures are special.
你们也见过吧
I think that you've seen that, too.
虽然
Now,
我帮这家公司干了不少坏事 但…
I've done some bad things for this company. But this...
这次别想
No way. Okay?
我受够他们的肮脏事
I'm done doing their dirty work.
帮助我们离开这里
Okay, then help us get them out of here.
送他们回家
We need to get them home.
不容易
It's not that simple.
要开50哩崎岖路段到火山口
Okay. It's 50 miles of rough terrain back to the vent.
开大卡车载他们
Any truck big enough to carry them
太慢 会被追上
would be too slow and we'd get caught.
我的卡车够快 只要再找两辆
I got a truck fast enough. We just gotta find two more.
如果你们觉得可行就算我一份
If you think we can do this, I'm in.
可以的
We can.
好 击掌
Okay, hands in.
抱歉 你流好多手汗
I'm sorry. You're just so sweaty.
威德斯先生
Mr. Weathers,
有好多怪事发生
there's a lot of really weird stuff going on right now
我需要你的帮忙
and I need your help.
你需要什么？
What do you need?
卡车
I need trucks.
你有哪些车还没收到钱？
Do you have any on your repo list?
不是我们的错 谁叫他还没付钱
It's not our fault rich boy can't make his payments.
太好了
Yeah!
嘭
Boom!
快点反击啊
Show me something! Come on!
继续追击
Yeah! Keep tagging him!
所有车子
I don't see anything on this
都装不下仓库那个大块头
that will carry that big sucker I saw in the warehouse.
你要怎么改装这些车？
What are you gonna need to do to these trucks?
这样
Well,
抬高引擎和悬挂系统
lift the engine, raise the suspension,
切割车身 特制轮轴
cut up the body, customize the axles,
加大气流 在明早之前重覆两次动作
and maximize the airflow. All by morning. Twice.
或许可以搞定一辆 但是有两辆？
Maybe we'd get one done, but two?
我的工具和零件没办法这么快
I don't have the tools or the parts to get it done that quick.
你有认识开修车厂的朋友吗？
Do you know someone with a repair shop?
- 或者… - 汽车经销商
- Or... - A dealership.
你以后要多跟他出去
You know, you're going to have to, like, hang out with him and stuff after this.
仅限一次
Maybe once.
七点可以离开吧？
You'll be out by 7:00, right?
早班工人七点会来
The first workers get here at 7:00.
可以
Yeah.
哪一辆是最好的卡车？
What's the best truck you got on the lot?
那会是我16岁的生日礼物
Well, it's supposed to be my 16th birthday present.
先看一眼没关系吧？
No harm getting an early peek, right?
你可以吗？
Can you handle one of these?
可以
Uh, yeah.
小心点 这很难驾驭
Be careful, it'll run away from you.
尽量喝
Here you go. Drink up.
我们要赶远路
We're going on a little road trip.
可以帮我搞定这个吗？
Hey, man, you mind helping me out with this?
好的 好的
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
快点 抬起来
Come on, man. Let's pick it up.
把它们弄到污水槽
Got to get those things to the waste-water tank
运出去
before they ship out.
干嘛一直叫？
What's got into these things?
嘿
Hey!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
对不起 对不起
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
叫柏克听电话
Yeah, get Burke on the phone.
追踪那辆大型厢式卡车
And start a trace on the box truck. The big one.
窦德
Dowd.
我把他们带来了 但时间不多了
Hey, I got them, but there's not much time.
坦纳森可能已经派柏克来找我们
Tenneson probably already has Burke coming for us.
干得好
Hey. Nice job.
谢谢
Thank you.
我第一次开手排挡车 太刺激了
I never drove a stick before. It was very exciting.
- 可以帮个忙吗？- 好啊
- Cool. Want to give me a hand with this? - Yeah.
哇哦
Wow.
天啊
Well, I'll be...
还好吧？
Hey, there.
你看起来很好
You're looking good.
跟你们同类比起来
For you.
好啦 好啦
Okay. Okay.
我想你
Yeah, I missed you.
我也想你
I missed you, too.
他们是一家人
They're a family.
原来他在找爸妈
He was looking for his parents.
我找到那辆卡车 它停下来了
I got the truck. It's stationary.
上车 走吧 找到他们了
Load up! Let's go! We got them!
没有回头路
No turning back now.
好了 这辆是你的
All right, this one's yours.
我要一起去吗？
Someone say I'm coming with you?
当然 我们需要你
Come on, man, we need you.
好吧
Okay.
反正都要坐牢了 还不如酷一点
If I'm going to go to prison, it might as well be in style.
上面标了火山口的位置 我会跟着你
Okay. The vents are marked on this. I'll follow you.
好的
Yeah.
你说这些家伙有群体智慧吧？
You said these guys have hive intelligence, right?
是啊
Yeah.
他知道该怎么做
Well, then he'll know what to do.
你只要引导他
You're just there to guide him.
- 是啊 - 温柔而坚定的
- Right. - Be gentle, but firm.
原来门可以开
That opens.
让他知道你才是驾驶
Let him know you're the one steering.
好 温柔而坚定 我才是驾驶
Right. Gentle but firm. I'm the one steering.
呃… 好吧
Uh... Okay.
嘿
Hey!
去吧
Go do this. Yeah.
谢谢你 威德斯先生
Thanks, Mr. Weathers.
你应该有从我身上学到怎么开卡车吧
Hope you picked something up from watching me.
一个礼拜前 你还在骑脚踏车呢
A week ago, you were riding a bicycle.
欢迎莅临盖登道奇
Uh... Welcome to Geldon Dodge.
要喝咖啡吗？
Can we get you a cup of complimentary coffee?
他们动身了
They're on the move.
什么？
What?
下一张投影片呢？
What about the next slide?
他们要去哪里？
They're on the move in what?
"坏孩子"
他们等不及要放风了
These guys were ready for a walk.
他们很开心 快要回家了
They're happy they're going home.
警方扫描器找到他们的位置
We just picked them up on a police scanner.
刀匠路
Off Old Cutler Road.
南方约一哩处
It's close, about a mile south.
他们在那里 十点钟方向
There they are. Ten o'clock.
开始了
Here we go.
我竟然让你和你女朋友说服我
I can't believe I let you and your girlfriend talk me into this.
我们不是…
Uh, we're not... That's not, uh...
我们是吗？
Are we?
警长 泰德盖洛威通报
Hey, Sheriff, we got a call from Ken Galloway.
有一堆卡车在他的地盘撒野
Said a bunch of trucks rode over his land.
似乎是怪兽卡车
He said they looked like monster trucks.
他们往哪里走？
Yeah, which way were they headed?
先搞定亮绿色那台
Okay, let's take out Big Green first.
我去左边
I'll take left.
收到 我去右边
Roger that. Taking right.
哦噢
Uh-oh.
他需要帮忙
He needs help.
开到后面去推他
Get behind him, Meredith. Give him a push.
什么？
Oh, what?
希望他们都有系安全带
Oh, I really hope they had their seat-belts on.
我们在平地跑不过他们
We can't outrun them in the flats.
但是在崎岖路段可以甩掉他们
Just hang on. We'll lose them in the rough.
跟紧 路要变窄了
Stay close here, guys. It's going to get tight.
在山脊拿下他们
We'll get them on the ridge.
我们知道要往哪里走吗？
Do we know where we're going?
别担心 他们知道
Don't worry, they know.
正前方有倒下的树
Uh, downed tree, dead ahead! Do we have a tree plan?
好 大伙拉起方向盘
Okay, guys. And pull!
窦德 可以张开眼睛了
Okay, Dowd, you can open your eyes now.
我们成功了？
Did We make it?
跟紧 路要变窄了
Everybody, stay close. It's going to get tight up here.
他们在我后面
They're right behind me!
崔普 你的右边
Tripp, on your right!
好 兜风之旅就要结束了
All right, kid, this is where your little joyride ends!
帮我
Help!
崔普
Tripp!
谢谢你 老弟
Thanks, buddy!
崔普 还好吗？
Tripp, are you okay?
还好 我…
Yeah, yeah. I'm...
那是什么？
What is that?
坦纳森
Oh, Tenneson.
是毒 我们要阻止
It's poison! We gotta stop that tanker.
他们污染栖地
They're going to poison the nest.
好吧 动作快一点
Okay. We need to move faster.
快点
Oh, come on!
点燃吧
Light it up.
后退
Get back! Stay back!
他们被困住了
We got 'em now!
看到他们了 从左边包抄
I see 'em! Go up the left side!
瑞克？
Rick?
靠边 靠边
Get to the sides! Get to the sides!
真不敢相信你来了 很高兴看到你
I cannot believe you're here. I'm actually really happy to see you.
我不是说我一直都会在吗？
Hey, I told you I wasn't going anywhere.
火山口在另一侧
The vents are right on the other side.
我们要越过这辆车
We have to get past this truck. It's the only way.
崔普 前方路况很不理想
Hang, on, Tripp, you're not seeing what I'm seeing.
不 我有GPS 我知道前方有什么
No, I got it right here. I know what we're in for.
你该不会要我们跳下去
I seriously hope you're not thinking about jumping off a mountain.
我不觉得他们做得到
As the only scientist here, I don't think they can do that.
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
希望你知道自己在干什么
I hope you know what you're doing, Tripp.
瑞克 想办法让我们跳过去吧
Rick, give us something to jump.
好
Yeah. Okay.
99％会失败
Tripp, there's a 99% chance that would be impossible.
搞不好是100%
Maybe 100%.
小心一点 小子
You be careful, son.
我很抱歉说过你那么多坏话
Rick, I'm sorry I said all those terrible things about you.
慢着 什么？
Wait, what?
我们走
Let's go!
来吧 曲奇
Come on, Creech!
冲啊 崔普
Go, Tripp!
我们成功了
We made it!
你们去摧毁帮浦 我来处理油罐车
You guys take out the pumps, I'll handle the tanker.
- 知道了 - 交给我们
- Got it. - We're on it.
那边还有一个
Hey, there's another one.
帮浦高速运转
Pumps are at speed!
快阻止他们
We need to stop those pumps.
最后冲刺 你就快到家啰
Come on. One last push. You're almost home.
哇
Whoa.
拦下所有开往火山口的卡车
Any trucks still running, get up here to the vents.
- 关得掉吗？- 控制板被锁住了
- Can we stop it? - Ah. It locked me out.
压力达到15,000 psi
If this pressure gets to 15,000 psi,
毒素就会抵达栖地
the poison will reach all the way down to the nest.
快点起来 你可以的
Come on, buddy, wake up! You can do it!
控制阀
The valves!
快点
Come on, come on!
顺时针转
Righty-tighiy.
我们要阻止毒素扩散
We have to stop the poison!
没用 太迟了
It's networking! We're too late!
你走 先救你自己
Go! Get out! Save yourself!
崔普
Tripp!
我们成功了
We did it.
我会想你的 曲奇
I'm going to miss you, Creech.
你是一辆好卡车
You were a good truck.
别担心 我知道怎么找到你
Don't worry. I know where to find you.
崔普
Tripp!
待在原地 我们来救你
You stay put. We got you.
鱼类和野生动物局吗？
Hi, Fish and Wildlife?
我和朋友在特拉维克斯
Yeah, my friends and I found some horned lizards
的土地发现角蜥
on the Terravex property.
它们是不是濒临绝种动物？
Are they endangered, by any chance?
"保护地环境敏感区"
比不上我之前那一辆
Well, it's nothing like my old one,
但够用了
but I think it'll do.
是啊
Yeah.
今年暑假你想干嘛就干嘛
Now you can do whatever you want this summer.
开去你想去的地方吧
Take it as far as it'll go.
谢谢你 瑞克
Thanks, Rick.